(Penny:)Kim, the night manager,
went on maternity leave...
(Penny:)...and her husband's name is Sandy.
(Penny:)So get this, her replacement
is a woman named Sandy...
(Penny:)...whose husband's name is Kim.
[CHORTLING]
(Leonard:)-Wow.
-I know. What are the odds? Oh.
(Sheldon:)Easily calculable. We begin by identifying
the set of couples with unisex names.
We eliminate those unqualified
for restaurant work:
(Sheldon:)the aged, the imprisoned
and the limbless, for example.
-Next, we look at the--
LEONARD: Sheldon.
(Leonard:)It's an amazing coincidence.
Can we leave it at that?
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Penny, it's as if the Cheesecake
Factory is run by witches.
(Penny:)Oh, Sheldon, it's as if you don't think
I'll punch you.
(Leonard:)Come on, you guys. Let it go.
(Penny:)Fine, whatever.
(Penny:)Are you finished?
(Sheldon:)Well, thank you. How thoughtful.